The ghosts of your past would like to have a word with you.
Brooklyn 45 is a horror, thriller, history film directed by Ted Geoghegan.
Five military veterans, best friends since childhood, gather together in a Brooklyn brownstone several months
after the end of World War II, and the metaphoric ghosts of their past become all-too-literal.
Marla Sheridan, played by Anne Ramsay.
Mjr. Paul DiFranco, played by Ezra Buzzington.
Mjr. Archibald Stanton, played by Jeremy Holm.
Lt. Col. Clive Hockstatter, played by Larry Fessenden.
Bob Sheridan, played by Ron E. Rains.
Hildegard Baumann, played by Kristina Klebe.
Brooklyn 45 is a 2023 American real-time supernatural thriller film written and directed by Ted Geoghegan about a group of
military veterans holding an impromptu séance in the parlor of a Brooklyn brownstone at the close of World War II.
Geoghegan penned the screenplay with assistance from his late father,
a disabled Air Force veteran-turned-history teacher.
The tone is dark and intense.